In America's darkest hour came an unlikely hero.
LBJ is a drama, history film directed by Rob Reiner.
The story of U.S.
President Lyndon Baines Johnson from his young days
in West Texas to the White House.
Lyndon B. Johnson, played by Woody Harrelson.
Robert F. Kennedy, played by Michael Stahl-David.
Sen. Richard Russell, played by Richard Jenkins.
Lady Bird Johnson, played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
John F. Kennedy, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Ralph Yarborough, played by Bill Pullman.
LBJ is a 2016 American political drama film about the
beginning of the administration of U.S.
President Lyndon B.
Johnson following the assassination of U.S.
President John F.
It was directed by Rob Reiner and written by Joey
Hartstone, whose script was on the 2014 Black List.
The film stars Woody Harrelson as Johnson, along with Richard Jenkins, Bill Pullman, Kim
Allen, Michael Stahl-David, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Jeffrey Donovan, Doug McKeon, C.
Thomas Howell, and Michael Mosley.
Principal photography took place in New Orleans, Baton
Rouge, Dallas, and Washington, D.C.
from September to December 2015.
The film premiered at the Toronto International
Film Festival on September 9, 2016.
It was theatrically released by Electric Entertainment and
Vertical Entertainment on November 3, 2017.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, who called it "surface skimming" and criticized Harrelson's
makeup, with some comparing the film negatively to the 2016 HBO film about Johnson, All the Way.
The film explores themes of usa president, the white house, civil
rights, dallas, texas, political assassination.
The tone is emotional.